Sarah Bankole

Brooklyn, New York
347.416.1218 | <u>sbankole312@gmail.com</u>
https://www.linkedin.com/in/sarahbankole123/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

IT Professional with more than five years of proven experience in technical consulting, customer service and operations support. Familiar with software testing principles and practices.. Experience in test case development and requirement analysis. Career supported by a Bachelor of Art in Studio Art as well as the pursuit of various technical training programs.

• Detail Oriented

Software Testing

Critical Thinking Skills

• Familiar with Jira

Agile Methodologies

Microsoft Operating Systems

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript Cloud Computing: GitHub Copilot ChatGPT

Software: React, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Jira, Epic, EClinicalWorks

Operating Systems: Windows 10, Mac OSX, Android/iOS

Hardware: iMac, MacBooks iPhone, iPad, Android/Samsung phones and tablets, Windows laptops and desktops

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Manual QA Tester, Saldo Tech

2024-2024

- Created and executed manual test cases based on client specifications.
- Identified 97% of software defects and inconsistencies on assigned sections.
- Collaborated with QA team and developers to understand project requirements, functionality and ensure bug-free application
- Provided recommendations on ways to improve user experience.

Medical Receptionist, Babok Medical Services

2021 - 2024

- Maintained accurate and secure patient data; ensured accuracy in medical records and documentation
- Managed patient records and appointments, streamlining processes and improving accuracy, akin to
 organizing and managing project tasks to enhance efficiency and deliver successful outcomes in
 development projects.
- Collaborated with healthcare professionals and patients to ensure clear and efficient communication
- Increased patient data management efficiency through proficient use of electronic health records (EHR) systems and other healthcare software.

Consultant, Epic Go Live Support

2016 - 2020

- Led team of six in providing comprehensive elbow support to end users and super users during go-live project resulting in a 15% decrease in post-implementation support tickets.
- Participated in user meetings in order to prioritize reviews and requests leading to a 25% improvement in user satisfaction.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams, including IT specialists and system administrators, to escalate complex issues, coordinate resolutions, and implement preventive measures to enhance system stability and user experience.
- Helped troubleshoot problems and questions from medical staff during go live, resolving over 80% of issues
 on the first contact.

TECHNICAL TRAINING

Path2TECH Trainee | NPower

- Completing an intensive 20-week Full Stack Developer training program, gaining hands-on experience in both front-end and back-end development technologies, including HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Developing proficiency in building responsive and interactive user interfaces using popular front-end frameworks such as React.js, ensuring a seamless user experience across various devices.
- Acquiring essential back-end development skills through practical training in server-side scripting with Node.js, utilizing Express.js for efficient routing and building scalable web applications.
- Acquiring the ability to work with databases by mastering fundamental database management concepts and hands-on experience with MongoDB, ensuring effective storage and retrieval of data.
- Collaborated with peers on real-world projects, applying Agile development methodologies, version control using Git, and participating in regular code reviews, fostering a collaborative environment.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Path2TECH | nPower | In Pursuit Bachelors of Arts in Studio Art | Hunter College | Graduated

Certifications

Obtained: Pursuing: Google Automation with Python Certificate